Digital Collections and Archives Records UA069
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Digital objects, 1662 -- 2015; 2000 -- 2004; UA069.005; 542 Digital Object(s)
  - Accounting To Whom For What?, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00295; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Accounting To Whom For What?," written by Walter B. Wriston for the National Association of Accountants on 21 June 1976. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00008.
    Accounting; Accounting Standards; Wriston, Walter B.
  - People, Politics and Productivity: The World Corporation in the 1980s, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00296; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "People, Politics and Productivity: The World Corporation in the 1980s," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Multinational Customer Conference on 15 September 1976. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00009.
    International business enterprises; Economics.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Outlook for the U.S. Economy, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00297; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Outlook for the U.S. Economy," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Sedlabanki Islands Luncheon on 2 May 1977. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00014.
  - Let's Create Wealth, Not Allocate Shortages, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00298; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Let's Create Wealth, Not Allocate Shortages," written by Walter B. Wriston for the United Nations' Ambassadors' Dinner on 24 May 1977. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00015.
    Developing countries; Investments; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Testimony of Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00299; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Testimony of Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the New York State Assembly Committee on Banking on 11 October 1977. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00019.
    Finance, Public New York (State) New York; Budget New York (State) New York; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Protecting Trade From Protectionism, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00300; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Protecting Trade From Protectionism," written by Walter B. Wriston for a speaking engagement in Brussels on 24 October 1977. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00021.
  - Wriston--Wharton, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00301; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Wriston--Wharton," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Wharton School Club on 20 March 1979. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00031.
    Public Interest; Awards; Wriston, Walter B.
  - If You Ask Me: A Global Banker Reflects on Our Times, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00302; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from a compilation of interviews and question and answer segments with Walter B. Wriston which was later compiled into "If You Ask Me: A Global Banker Reflects on Our Times" in 1980. The original speech is located in MS134.001.034.00018.
  - Fletcher in the Information Age, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00303; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Fletcher in the Information Age," written by Walter B. Wriston for convocation at the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy at Tufts University on 3 September 2003. The original speech is located in MS134.001.015.00002.
  - Statement by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00304; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Statement by Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs on 29 October 1981. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00034.
    Banks and banking; Banking law United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Hooray for Hollywood, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00305; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Hooray for Hollywood," written by Walter B. Wriston for the 1981 Chamber of Commerce Business Conference on 10 November 1981. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00035.
    Banking law United States; Banks and banking; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks at Washington Business Group on Health Annual Conference, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00306; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks at Washington Business Group on Health Annual Conference," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Washington Business Group on Health Annual Conference on 23 June 1982. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00002.
    Medical care United States; Technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Information Society: From Gutenberg to S.W.I.F.T., 2007; UA069.005.DO.00307; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech,"The Information Society: From Gutenberg to S.W.I.F.T.," written by Walter B. Wriston for the S.W.I.F.T. Conference SIBOS '82 on 23 September 1982. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00004.
    Technology; Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Acceptance Speech for the Civic Commitment Award, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00308; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech,"Acceptance Speech for the Civic Commitment Award," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Anti-Defamation League on 7 October 1980. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00020.
    Awards; Citicorp; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Personal Reflections on the State of the Board: What's right and what's wrong with the current system of corporate oversight: Interviews with Reginald Jones, Walter Wriston, and Victor Palmieri, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00309; Kristies, James
    This document was created from the article, "Personal Reflections on the State of the Board: What's right and what's wrong with the current system of corporate oversight: Interviews with Reginald Jones, Walter Wriston, and Victor Palmieri" by Walter B. Wriston for the Fall 1986 edition of "Directors and Boards." The original article is located in MS134.003.026.00030.
    Board of directors; Leadership; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Oil Shock Plus 5! A Reassessment, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00310; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech,"The Oil Shock Plus 5! A Reassessment," written by Walter B. Wriston for the U.S. Chamber of Commerce of Sao Paulo on 14 September 1978. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00027.
    Economics.; Petroleum industry and trade; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Domestic International Banking Units, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00311; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech,"Domestic International Banking Units," written by Walter B. Wriston for the New School Banking Course on 19 March 1979. The original speech is located in MS134.001.003.00030.
    International Trade; Banks and banking, International; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Chrysler Corporation Statement, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00312; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Chrysler Corporation Statement," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs on 21 November 1979. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00005.
    Chrysler Corporation; Loans; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks at the Financial Accounting Standards Board, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00313; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks at the Financial Accounting Standards Board," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Public Hearing on Accounting by Debtors and Creditors When Debt is Restructured circa 1980s. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00007.
    Accounting Standards; Banks and banking; Wriston, Walter B.
  - From the Hall of Mirrors to the Floppy Disc, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00314; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "From the Hall of Mirrors to the Floppy Disc," written by Walter B. Wriston for the National Bureau of Economic Research on 3 January 1980. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00010.
  - Let's Stop Making the Wrong Mistakes, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00315; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Let's Stop Making the Wrong Mistakes," written by Walter B. Wriston for the 1980 Banking Forum on 26 January 1980. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00011.
  - Introduction for Edward Seaga, Prime Minister of Jamaica, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00316; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Introduction for Edward Seaga, Prime Minister of Jamaica," written by Walter B. Wriston to introduce Edward Seaga, Prime Minister of Jamaica on 8 July 1981. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00031.
    Jamaica Economic policy; Economics.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Scorner's Seat: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00317; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Scorner's Seat: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy on 30 September 1982. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00005.
  - Testimony of Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00318; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Testimony of Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations of the Committee on Energy and Commerce House of Representatives on 28 June 1983. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00014.
    Citicorp; Corporate governance; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Bankers and Plato's Cave Shadow and Substance, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00319; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Bankers and Plato's Cave Shadow and Substance," written by Walter B. Wriston for the American Bankers Association on 10 October 1983. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00016.
    Banks and banking; Competition; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Model for Perpetual Motion, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00320; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Model for Perpetual Motion," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Executive Dinner Forum on 24 May 1984. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00020.
    Entrepreneurship; Technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Contemporary Journalism, a Sermon, a Chill Down the Spine, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00321; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Contemporary Journalism, a Sermon, a Chill Down the Spine," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Peat-Marwick Banking Directions Seminar on 24 September 1984. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00026.
    Banks and banking; Technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Looking Backward-Going Forward, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00322; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Looking Backward-Going Forward," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Insurance Forum on 18 November 1982. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00009.
    Technology; Financial Services Industry; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Law Business and Business and the Law, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00323; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Law Business and Business and the Law," written by Walter B. Wriston for the American Bar Association on 26 October 1984. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00028.
    Lawyers; Business; Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Great Disconnect: Balance Sheets vs. Market Value, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00324; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Great Disconnect: Balance Sheets vs. Market Value," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Cap Gemini Center for Business Ernst & Young Innovations Conference on 2 October 2000. The original speech is located in MS134.001.014.00012.
  - The Future is Unbelievable, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00325; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Future is Unbelievable," written by Walter B. Wriston for Citibank on 18 November 1999. The original speech is located in MS134.001.014.00008.
  - The Technology of Freedom, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00326; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Technology of Freedom," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Mont Pelerin Society on the 100th Anniversary of the Birth of Friedrich Hayek on 1 September 1999. The original speech is located in MS134.001.014.00007.
  - Shadow and Reality: The Quick and The Dead, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00327; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Shadow and Reality: The Quick and The Dead," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Fortune Financial Services Technology Forum on 4 March 1999. The original speech is located in MS134.001.014.00004.
  - Rules for a Wired World, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00328; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Rules for a Wired World," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Manhattan Institute for Policy Research on 6 October 1998. The original speech is located in MS134.001.014.00002.
    Technology; Economics.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Two Lucky People, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00329; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Two Lucky People," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Rose and Milton Friedman Dinner on 22 July 1998. The original speech is located in MS134.001.014.00001.
    Friedman, Milton, 1919-2006; Friedman, Rose D.; Economics.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Shearman & Sterling and Citibank Yesterday and Tomorrow, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00330; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Shearman & Sterling and Citibank Yesterday and Tomorrow," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Boca Raton Resort and Club on 24 April 1998. The original speech is located in MS134.001.013.00008.
    Shearman & Sterling; Citicorp; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Bits, Bytes, Power & Diplomacy, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00331; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Bits, Bytes, Power & Diplomacy," written by Walter B. Wriston for the United States Institute of Peace 1 April 1997. The original speech is located in MS134.001.013.00006.
  - The Whisky Ain't Working Any More, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00332; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Whisky Ain't Working Any More," written by Walter B. Wriston for Perspective 95 on 14 September 1995. The original speech is located in MS134.001.012.00008.
    Technology; Information technology; Financial Services Industry; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Acceptance Speech for the Patriot Award, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00333; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Acceptance Speech for the Patriot Award," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Sons of the Revolution Patriot Award Dinner on 21 February 1992. The original speech is located in MS134.001.010.00006.
    Awards; History; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Doing Business in the Information Age, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00334; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Doing Business in the Information Age," written by Walter B. Wriston for the DMA [Direct Marketing Association] Annual Financial Service Conference on 8 June 1989. The original speech is located in MS134.001.009.00011.
  - Elites, Electrons and Deregulation, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00335; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Elites, Electrons and Deregulation," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Institutional Investors Conference on 14 June 1985. The original speech is located in MS134.001.006.00009.
  - You Push the First valve Down, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00336; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "You Push the First valve Down," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Fellows of the Academy of International Business on 18 October 1985. The original speech is located in MS134.001.007.00001.
    Business; Law United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00337; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks by Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Vintage Club Post Election Conference on 15 November 1984. The original speech is located in MS134.001.006.00003.
  - Price Vs. Policy: A Tale of Two Markets, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00338; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Price Vs. Policy: A Tale of Two Markets," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Seventh Annual International Trade Conference on 8 April 1980. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00014.
    Petroleum industry and trade; Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries; Developing countries; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Acceptance Speech for the Citation of Merit Award, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00339; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Acceptance Speech for the Citation of Merit Award," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Salvation Army Association of Greater New York on 3 December 1980. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00023.
  - Money - Back to the Future?, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00340; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Money - Back to the Future?," written by Walter B. Wriston for Claremont McKenna College on 20 November 1996. The original speech is located in MS134.001.013.00003.
    Monetary policy United States; Currency question; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00341; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks by Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Financial Executives Institute on 3 March 1987. The original speech is located in MS134.001.008.00002.
  - Mistress of the World, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00342; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Mistress of the World," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Freedom Forum on 25 October 1993. The original speech is located in MS134.001.011.00005.
  - Never Do Anything for the First Time, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00343; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Never Do Anything for the First Time," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Nolan Norton Symposium on 16 January 1986. The original speech is located in MS134.001.007.00004.
  - The Information Standard, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00344; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Information Standard," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Business Council on 10 October 1986. The original speech is located in MS134.001.007.00010.
    International finance; Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Looking Backward at the Nineteen-Eighties, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00345; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Looking Backward at the Nineteen-Eighties," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Reserve City Bankers on 31 March 1980. The original speech is located in MS134.001.004.00013.
  - Remarks of Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00346; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks of Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for Shearman & Sterling LLP on 23 January 1983. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00012.
    Financial Services Industry; Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Good News/Bad News/Instant Data, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00347; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Good News/Bad News/Instant Data," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Hong Kong Chamber of Commerce on 3 October 1983. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00015.
    Technology; Hong Kong (China); Wriston, Walter B.
  - The Citi of Tomorrow: Today, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00348; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Citi of Tomorrow: Today," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Bank and Financial Analysts Association on 7 March 1984. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00018.
  - Remarks by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00349; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks by Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the International Institute of Communication on 13 September 1988. The original speech is located in MS134.001.009.00004.
  - Remarks by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00350; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks by Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Nolan-Norton Symposium on 19 September 1988. The original speech is located in MS134.001.009.00005.
    Business; Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00351; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks by Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Business Council on 13 October 1988. The original speech is located in MS134.001.009.00007.
    Budget deficits United States; United States Economic Policy; Wriston, Walter B.
  - New Wine in Old Bottles, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00352; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "New Wine in Old Bottles," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Indiana University School of Business on 18 April 1989. The original speech is located in MS134.001.009.00010.
    Economics.; Information technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00353; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks by Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Casualty Actuarial Society on 14 November 1989. The original speech is located in MS134.001.010.00003.
  - The Twilight of Sovereignty, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00354; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "The Twilight of Sovereignty," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Commonwealth Club on 10 November 1992. The original speech is located in MS134.001.010.00010.
  - Global Recovery and World Debt: An Address, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00355; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Global Recovery and World Debt: An Address," written by Walter B. Wriston for the International Monetary Conference on 4 June 1984. The original speech is located in MS134.001.005.00021.
  - Remarks by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00356; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks by Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the Digital Conference on 2 December 1987. The original speech is located in MS134.001.008.00011.
    Business; Information technology; Technology; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Remarks by Walter B. Wriston, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00357; Wriston, Walter B.
    The document was created from the speech, "Remarks by Walter B. Wriston," written by Walter B. Wriston for the National Service Retailers on 23 October 1987. The original speech is located in MS134.001.008.00009.
  - The Drive for Exports, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00358; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "The Drive for Exports," written by Walter B. Wriston for the August 1, 1963 edition of "American Banker." The original article is located in MS134.003.026.00009.
    International Trade; Balance of payments United States; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Wriston of Citicorp Is Still Plugged In, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00359
    This document was created from the article, "Wriston of Citicorp Is Still Plugged In," written by an unknown author for the 1996 edition of "FutureBanking." The original article is located in MS134.003.026.00003.
  - First Glance at BOP Program is Fine, But Administration's Borrowing Time, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00360; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "First Glance at BOP Program is Fine, But Administration's Borrowing Time," written by Walter B. Wriston for the February 28, 1966 edition of "American Banker." The original article is located in MS134.003.026.00011.